<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="status">Status field initial value</string>
    <string name="app_name">LTC</string>
    <string name="find_hint">Enter stop number or keywords, e.g. dundas well</string>
    <string name="stop_number">Stop #</string>
    <string name="stop_name">Stop Name</string>
    <string name="last_updated">Last updated</string>
    <string name="at_this_stop">At this stop: %1$s</string>
    <string name="stop_times">Stop Times</string>
    <string name="download_instructions">Downloading bus route and stop data takes about 2 minutes and uses between 1M and 2M of data. Downloading on wifi is recommended but not required.</string>
    <string name="update">Download</string>
    <string name="using_provider">Location provider: %1$s</string>
    <string name="no_provider">Location not available</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="about_text">
    Version 0.1 (alpha). Although this app uses data from the London Transit Commission (LTC) website it is
    not affiliated with the LTC. Do *not* report problems with this app to the LTC. Report problems
    to frasermccrossan@gmail.com.
    \n\nIf you have a problem with this app, I would like to hear from you
    and have an opportunity to fix it before you leave a bad review. This
    app is completely free to use and does not have ads.
    \n\nThis program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
    it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
    the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
    (at your option) any later version.
    \n\nThis program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
    but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
    MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
    GNU General Public License for more details.
    \n\nYou should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
    along with this program.  If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses/.
    \n\nHTML parsing using jsoup by Jonathan Hedley http://jsoup.org/
    \n\nLauncher icon adapted from \"Bus\" symbol by Roger Cook and Don Shanosky, AIGA, U.S. Department of Transportation, from thenounproject.com collection.
    \n\nAbout icon from \"Information\" symbol by Sven Hofmann, from thenounproject.com collection.
    \n\nSatellite icon from \"Satellite\" symbol by Jose Luis Algara, from thenounproject.com collection.
    \n\nAntenna icon from \"Antenna\" symbol by Christian Hohenfeld, from thenounproject.com collection.
    \n\nRefresh icon is \"Cloud Refresh\" by Adam Whitfield, from thenounproject.com.
    </string>
    <string name="stop_list_help_text">
    This screen shows stops matching the search text. If GPS is enabled, they are
    the stops closest to you, else they are the ones you have checked most often.
    \n\nIf the search is only digits, it matches both stop numbers (on the blue signs)
    and stops containing numbers (e.g. \"1102 Jalna NB\"). If there are any non-digits,
    it just matches stop names.
    \n\nCase is ignored, and multiple, partial words work. For example to find stops at Dundas and Richmond, try
    \"dun rich\".
    </string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="location_status">location status</string>
    <string name="refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="msg_idle">Wait</string>
    <string name="msg_querying">(Wait)</string>
    <string name="msg_fail">Fail</string>
    <string name="msg_bug">Bug</string>
    <string name="on_weekday">on a week-day</string>
    <string name="on_saturday">on a Saturday</string>
    <string name="on_sunday">on a Sunday</string>
    <string name="update_recommended">The bus route and stop database has not been generated for a while %s. An update is recommended.</string>
    <string name="update_required">The bus route and stop database has never been generated %s. An update is required.</string>
    <string name="update_not_required">The bus route and stop database has been recently generated %s. An update is not required unless you know that routes or stops have recently changed.</string>
    <string name="update_database">Update Database</string>

</resources>