<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="status">Status field initial value</string>
    <string name="app_name">LTC</string>
    <string name="long_app_name">LTC Buses</string>
    <string name="find_hint">Enter stop number or keywords, e.g. dundas well</string>
    <string name="stop_number">Stop #</string>
    <string name="stop_name">Stop Name</string>
    <string name="last_updated">Last updated</string>
    <string name="at_this_stop">At this stop: %1$s</string>
    <string name="stop_times">Stop Times</string>
    <string name="download_instructions">Downloading bus route and stop data takes about 2 minutes and uses between 1M and 2M of data. Downloading on wifi is recommended but not required.</string>
    <string name="update">Download</string>
    <string name="using_provider">Location provider: %1$s</string>
    <string name="no_provider">Location not available</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="about_text">
    <![CDATA[<html>
    <body>
    <h1>LTC Buses</h1>
    <h3>Version 0.2 (alpha) &copy; 2012 Fraser McCrossan</h3>
    <h2>Notice</h2>
    <p>
    Although this app uses data from the
    <a href="http://www.ltconline.ca/">London Transit Commission</a> (LTC) website it is
    not affiliated with the LTC. <em>Do not report problems with this app to the LTC.</em>
    This app may break suddenly and without warning if the LTC alter their
    <a href="http://www.ltconline.ca/WebWatch/">Webwatch</a> service.
    </p>
    <h2>If You Have Problems</h2>
    <p>
    If you have a problem with this app, I would like to hear from you
    and have an opportunity to fix it before you leave a bad review.
    Report problems
    at <a href="http://code.google.com/p/ltc-buses/issues/list">the issues page</a>, by email to
    <a href="mailto:frasermccrossan@gmail.com">frasermccrossan@gmail.com</a>,
    or by Twitter to <a href="https://twitter.com/joatca">@joatca</a>.
    This app is offered as a public service and is ad-free.
    Please help make it better! If you paid for this app, you have been swindled.
    </p>
    <h2>License</h2>
    <p>
    This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
    it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
    the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
    (at your option) any later version.
    </p>
    <p>
    This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
    but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
    MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
    GNU General Public License for more details.
    </p>
    <p>
    You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
    along with this program.  If not, see
    <a href="http://www.gnu.org/licenses/">http://www.gnu.org/licenses/</a>.
    </p>
    <h2>Acknowledgments</h2>
    <p>
    HTML parsing using <a href="http://jsoup.org/">jsoup</a> by Jonathan Hedley.
    </p>
    <p>
    Launcher icon adapted from \"Bus\" symbol by Roger Cook and Don Shanosky, AIGA,
    U.S. Department of Transportation, from <a href="http://thenounproject.com">The Noun Project</a> collection.
    </p>
    <p>
    About icon from \"Information\" symbol by Sven Hofmann,
    from <a href="http://thenounproject.com">The Noun Project</a> collection.
    </p>
    <p>
    Satellite icon from \"Satellite\" symbol by Jose Luis Algara,
    from <a href="http://thenounproject.com">The Noun Project</a> collection.
    </p>
    <p>
    Antenna icon from \"Antenna\" symbol by Christian Hohenfeld,
    from <a href="http://thenounproject.com">The Noun Project</a> collection.
    </p>
    <p>
    Refresh icon is \"Cloud Refresh\" by Adam Whitfield, from
    <a href="http://thenounproject.com">The Noun Project</a>.
    </body>
    </html>
    ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="stop_list_help_text">
    <![CDATA[<html>
    <body>
    <h2>List of Stops</h2>
    <p>
    If GPS is enabled, this screen shows the stops closest to you,
    else it shows the stops you have viewed most often. Tap a stop
    to show the next arrivals for all routes at the stop.
    </p>
    <h2>Searching</h2>
    <p>
    Enter text or numbers to search for a stop.
    If the search is only digits, it matches both stop numbers (on the blue signs)
    and stops containing numbers (e.g. \"1102 Jalna NB\"). If there are any non-digits,
    it just matches stop names.
    </p>
    <p>
    Case is ignored, and multiple, partial words work. For example to find stops at Dundas and Richmond, try
    \"dun rich\".
    </p>
    </body>
    </html>
    ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="location_status">location status</string>
    <string name="refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="msg_idle">Wait</string>
    <string name="msg_querying">(Wait)</string>
    <string name="msg_fail">Fail</string>
    <string name="msg_bug">Bug</string>
    <string name="on_weekday">on a weekday</string>
    <string name="on_saturday">on a Saturday</string>
    <string name="on_sunday">on a Sunday</string>
    <string name="update_recommended">The bus route and stop database has not been generated for a while %s. An update is recommended.</string>
    <string name="update_required">The bus route and stop database has never been generated %s. An update is required.</string>
    <string name="update_not_required">The bus route and stop database has been recently generated %s. An update is not required unless you know that routes or stops have recently changed.</string>
    <string name="update_database">Update Database</string>
    <string name="retrying">Connection took too long, retrying...</string>
    <string name="times_none">None</string>
    <string name="times_fail">[Failed]</string>
    <string name="times_timeout">[Timeout]</string>
    <string name="finding_routes">Finding routes...</string>

</resources>